https://www.helion.co.uk/privacy.php?sid=d1185f45ed8d55e73f4cf49e34806567

Delivery • Terms & Conditions
HomeNew TitlesForthcoming TitlesFeatured TitleseBooksAll TitlesPeriods21st Century
Helion Wargames
PeopleBlogEventsUpcoming Helion ConferencesUpcoming Trade ShowsPast Helion ConferencesContact Us
MenuNew TitlesForthcoming TitlesFeatured TitleseBooksAll TitlesPeriodsSeriesPeopleBlogUpcoming Helion ConferencesUpcoming Trade ShowsCreate an AccountSign-inNewsletterDeliveryTerms & ConditionsContact UsHome
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Helion & Company Limited uses and protects any information that you give Helion & Company Limited when you use this website.
Helion & Company Limited is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Helion & Company Limited may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 21 May 2018.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email and postal address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. We only send these to you if you have agreed to subscribe to our newsletter, i.e. opted-in to receiving them. If you wish to cease receiving these emails please follow the instructions to unsubscribe at the bottom of each e-newsletter.
Our lawful basis for processing the information we gather
Under the terms of the 2018 EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) we are required to explain the lawful basis for why we process the data, our data retention periods and your right to complain.
There are six lawful bases for processing data - Consent, Contract, Legal Obligation, Vital Interests, Public Task, Legitimate Interests. Further information on these can be found here: https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/lawful-basis-for-processing/. We process your data on the basis of the first three, i.e. Consent, Contract, Legal Obligation. Specifically, by ordering from or contacting us via the website you give us your consent to handle your personal data in such a way that we can fulfil your requirements. By ordering from this site both parties enter into a contract, therefore we will also process your data on the basis of a contractual basis. We may also be legally obliged to handle your data so that we comply with the law.
Data retention: any paper correspondence relating to individuals may be retained to comply with legal requirements. If this is not the case, it is shredded after seven years. Electronic data relating to individuals is retained on an ongoing basis in order for us to continue to provide services to you, for example retaining your address details on the Magento database which services this website, and allows you to view your customer account, order history and so forth.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
The following is a summary of the types of cookies that are being used on this site, along with information on how you can block them.
This site uses cookies placed by Google Analytics; this is a service offered by Google that tracks and reports website usage which we use to analyse visitor trends and improve our service to you.
As well as modifying your browser settings you can also opt out of Google Analytics here.
To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
Helion & Company Limited does not use Cookies to store information such as credit card numbers, telephone numbers, or other information you provide.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@helion.co.uk
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998 and under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2018. No fee is payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Helion & Company Limited, Unit 8 Amherst Business Centre, Budbrooke Road, Warwick CV34 5WE.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Quick Links
DeliveryFrequently Asked QuestionsDownloads inc. Catalogues & Paper SoldiersTrade InformationAuthor GuidelinesTerms & Conditions
Contact Us
Helion & CompanyUnit 8, Amherst Business CentreBudbrooke RoadWarwickCV34 5WE
01926 499619
info@helion.co.uk
© 2019 - 2020 Helion & Company Limited & SWD • Legal Info • Terms of Use • Privacy & Cookies
